emultimediatv.com 2018-12-14

# Privacy Policy-Emultimediatv.com

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how **their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in** US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website. 

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience. 

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you place an order or enter information on our site. 

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways: 

  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries).

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. Here we Scanning Malware Regularly. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information. All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers. 

**Do we use “cookies”?**

We do not use cookies for tracking purposes. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your **browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn** cookies off, some features will be disabled. That makes your site experience more efficient and may not function properly. However, you will still be able to place orders.
